{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"9.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":6651,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":58,"width":1136,"height":640,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index_scorm.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"BRIDGE ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"BRIDGE ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_3","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5298","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5318","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5126","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_2","Text_Caption_3","Image_3","SmartShape_1","si5298","si5318"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":153},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5126"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_4","title":"Let’s see what you know!   This is a PRE-TEST!  It will not be graded.  Look at the sentences and choose the correct answer.   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"Countries & Nationalities ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":"Take The Pre-Test ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5515","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Take The Pre-Test ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5535","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Take The Pre-Test ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5434","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_4","SmartShape_2","SmartShape_4","si5515","si5535"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":153},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5434"}}},{"id":"si7251","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5845q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_14","roles":{}},{"id":"si5714","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1","title":"Question 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5726","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"What’s this country? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5737","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_6","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5741","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"Mexico ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5737_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Canada\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5748","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5752","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"Brazil ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5748_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Brazil\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5835","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_1","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5845q0","for":"Slide5845q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5790","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5845q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5803","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5845q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5845","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si7251","Image_14","si5714","si5726","si5741","si5752","si5835","si5790","si5803"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5845"},"question":{"interactionId":"5694","quizId":383,"title":"Question 2\r","text":"What’s this country?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si7707","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7706q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_16","roles":{}},{"id":"si7575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_64","title":"Question 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7587","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_65","title":"What’s this country? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7598","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_66","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7602","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_67","title":"Canada ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7598_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_23","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Canada\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7609","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_68","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7613","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_69","title":"England ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7609_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_24","roles":{"answer":{"title":"England\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7696","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_11","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7706q1","for":"Slide7706q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7651","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_25","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7706q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7664","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_26","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7706q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7706","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si7707","Image_16","si7575","si7587","si7602","si7613","si7696","si7651","si7664"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7706"},"question":{"interactionId":"7555","quizId":383,"title":"Question 2\r","text":"What’s this country?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si7896","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7895q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_17","roles":{}},{"id":"si7764","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_70","title":"Question 3 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7776","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_71","title":"What’s this country? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7787","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_72","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7791","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_73","title":"Japan ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7787_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_25","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Japan\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7798","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_74","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7802","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_75","title":"Australia ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7798_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_26","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Australia\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7885","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_12","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7895q2","for":"Slide7895q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7840","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_27","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7895q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7853","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_28","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7895q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7895","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si7896","Image_17","si7764","si7776","si7791","si7802","si7885","si7840","si7853"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7895"},"question":{"interactionId":"7745","quizId":383,"title":"Question 3\r","text":"What’s this country?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si8081","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8080q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_18","roles":{}},{"id":"si7949","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_76","title":"Question 4 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7961","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_77","title":"What’s this country? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7972","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_78","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7976","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_79","title":"Saudi Arabia ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7972_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_27","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Saudi Arabia\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7983","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_80","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7987","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_81","title":"Vietnam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7983_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_28","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Vietnam\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_13","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8080q3","for":"Slide8080q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8025","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_29","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8080q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8038","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_30","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8080q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8080","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si8081","Image_18","si7949","si7961","si7976","si7987","si8070","si8025","si8038"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8080"},"question":{"interactionId":"7929","quizId":383,"title":"Question 4\r","text":"What’s this country?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si8266","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8265q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_19","roles":{}},{"id":"si8134","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_82","title":"Question 5 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8146","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_83","title":"What’s this country? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8157","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_84","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8161","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_85","title":"Spain ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8157_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_29","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Spain\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8168","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_86","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8172","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_87","title":"Mexico ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8168_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_30","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Mexico\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8255","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_14","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8265q4","for":"Slide8265q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8210","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_31","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8265q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8223","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_32","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8265q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8265","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si8266","Image_19","si8134","si8146","si8161","si8172","si8255","si8210","si8223"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8265"},"question":{"interactionId":"8114","quizId":383,"title":"Question 5\r","text":"What’s this country?\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si8451","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8450q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_20","roles":{}},{"id":"si8319","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_88","title":"Question 6 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_89","title":"A: Where are you from? B: I’m from China. A: You’re _________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8342","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_90","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8346","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_91","title":"Chinese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8342_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_31","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Chinese\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8353","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_92","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_93","title":"Chininian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8353_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_32","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Chininian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8440","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_15","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8450q5","for":"Slide8450q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8395","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_33","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8450q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8408","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_34","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8450q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8450","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si8451","Image_20","si8319","si8331","si8346","si8357","si8440","si8395","si8408"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8450"},"question":{"interactionId":"8299","quizId":383,"title":"Question 6\r","text":"A: Where are you from?\rB: I’m from China.\rA: You’re _________.\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si8632","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8631q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_21","roles":{}},{"id":"si8500","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_94","title":"Question 7 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8512","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_95","title":"A: Where are you from? B: I’m from Saudi Arabia. A: You’re _________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8523","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_96","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8527","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_97","title":"Saudian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8523_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_33","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Saudian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8534","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_98","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8538","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_99","title":"Saudi ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8534_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_34","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Saudi\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8621","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_16","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8631q6","for":"Slide8631q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8576","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_35","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8631q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8589","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_36","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8631q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8631","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si8632","Image_21","si8500","si8512","si8527","si8538","si8621","si8576","si8589"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8631"},"question":{"interactionId":"8480","quizId":383,"title":"Question 7\r","text":"A: Where are you from?\rB: I’m from Saudi Arabia.\rA: You’re _________.\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si8813","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8812q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_22","roles":{}},{"id":"si8681","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_100","title":"Question 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8693","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_101","title":"A: Where are you from? B: I’m from Peru. A: You’re _________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8704","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_102","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8708","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_103","title":"Perunese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8704_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_35","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Perunese\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8715","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_104","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8719","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_105","title":"Peruvian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8715_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_36","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Peruvian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8802","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_17","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8812q7","for":"Slide8812q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8757","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_37","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8812q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8770","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_38","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8812q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8812","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si8813","Image_22","si8681","si8693","si8708","si8719","si8802","si8757","si8770"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8812"},"question":{"interactionId":"8661","quizId":383,"title":"Question 8\r","text":"A: Where are you from?\rB: I’m from Peru.\rA: You’re _________.\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si8994","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8993q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_23","roles":{}},{"id":"si8862","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":"Question 9 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8874","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"A: Where are you from? B: I’m from Portugal. A: You’re _________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8885","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_108","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8889","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_109","title":"Portuguese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8885_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_37","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Portuguese\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8896","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_110","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8900","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_111","title":"Portuginian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8896_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_38","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Portuginian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8983","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_18","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8993q8","for":"Slide8993q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8938","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_39","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8993q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8951","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_40","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8993q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8993","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si8994","Image_23","si8862","si8874","si8889","si8900","si8983","si8938","si8951"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8993"},"question":{"interactionId":"8842","quizId":383,"title":"Question 9\r","text":"A: Where are you from?\rB: I’m from Portugal.\rA: You’re _________.\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si9175","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9174q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_24","roles":{}},{"id":"si9043","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_112","title":"Question 10 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9055","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_113","title":"A: Where are you from? B: I’m from Spain. A: You’re _________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9066","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_114","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_115","title":"Spainian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9066_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_39","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Spainian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9077","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_116","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9081","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_117","title":"Spanish ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9077_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_40","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Spanish\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si9164","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_19","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide9174q9","for":"Slide9174q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9119","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_41","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9174q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_42","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide9174q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9174","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si9175","Image_24","si9043","si9055","si9070","si9081","si9164","si9119","si9132"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9174"},"question":{"interactionId":"9023","quizId":383,"title":"Question 10\r","text":"A: Where are you from?\rB: I’m from Spain.\rA: You’re _________.\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"SmartShape_43","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_43","title":"Countries ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_24","title":"Countries ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_23","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9274","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9294","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7250","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_43","SmartShape_24","SmartShape_23","si9274","si9294"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":183},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7250"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_44","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9444","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"China ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9455","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_45","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Portugal ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9513","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_46","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9560","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Brazil ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9571","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_47","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9618","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Canada ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9629","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_48","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_48","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9676","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The  United States ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9687","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_49","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_49","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9735","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The  United Kingdom ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9746","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_50","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_50","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9793","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Mexico ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9804","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_51","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_51","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9852","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Chile ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9863","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_52","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_52","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9910","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Saudi Arabia ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9921","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_53","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_53","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9968","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Spain ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9979","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_54","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_54","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10027","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Peru ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10038","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_55","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_55","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10085","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Japan ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10096","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_56","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_56","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10143","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Korea ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10154","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_57","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_57","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10201","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Vietnam ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10212","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_58","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_58","title":"Click To Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10247","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Click To Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10258","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Click To Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_59","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_59","title":"Click Each Country’s Flag  and Repeat ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10297","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_44","si9444","si9455","SmartShape_45","si9502","si9513","SmartShape_46","si9560","si9571","SmartShape_47","si9618","si9629","SmartShape_48","si9676","si9687","SmartShape_49","si9735","si9746","SmartShape_50","si9793","si9804","SmartShape_51","si9852","si9863","SmartShape_52","si9910","si9921","SmartShape_53","si9968","si9979","SmartShape_54","si10027","si10038","SmartShape_55","si10085","si10096","SmartShape_56","si10143","si10154","SmartShape_57","si10201","si10212","SmartShape_58","si10247","si10258","SmartShape_59"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":123},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10297"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_60","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_60","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10363","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10374","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_61","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_61","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10419","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10430","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_62","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_62","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10475","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10486","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_63","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10531","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10542","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_64","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_64","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10587","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_65","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_65","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10644","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10655","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_66","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_66","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10700","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10711","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_67","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_67","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10757","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10768","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_68","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_68","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10813","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10824","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_69","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_69","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10869","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_70","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_70","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10926","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10937","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_71","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_71","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10982","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10993","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_72","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_72","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11038","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11049","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_73","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_73","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11090","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11102","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_74","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_74","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11147","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11158","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_75","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_75","title":"Click To Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11193","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Click To Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11204","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Click To Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11215","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_76","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_76","title":"Where are you from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11242","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_77","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_77","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11282","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I’m from Japan ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11293","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I’m from Saudi Arabia ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11304","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I’m from Canada ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11315","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I’m from China ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11326","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I’m from Portugal ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11337","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I’m from Mexico ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11348","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I’m from Vietnam ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11359","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I’m from Korea ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11370","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I’m from Brazil ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11381","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I’m from The United States ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11392","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I’m from The United Kingdom ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11403","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I’m from Peru ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11414","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I’m from Chile ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11425","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"I’m from Spain ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_78","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_78","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11452","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Congratulations! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11468","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_60","si10363","si10374","SmartShape_61","si10419","si10430","SmartShape_62","si10475","si10486","SmartShape_63","si10531","si10542","SmartShape_64","si10587","si10598","SmartShape_65","si10644","si10655","SmartShape_66","si10700","si10711","SmartShape_67","si10757","si10768","SmartShape_68","si10813","si10824","SmartShape_69","si10869","si10880","SmartShape_70","si10926","si10937","SmartShape_71","si10982","si10993","SmartShape_72","si11038","si11049","SmartShape_73","si11079","si11090","si11102","SmartShape_74","si11147","si11158","SmartShape_75","si11193","si11204","si11215","SmartShape_76","si11242","SmartShape_77","si11282","si11293","si11304","si11315","si11326","si11337","si11348","si11359","si11370","si11381","si11392","si11403","si11414","si11425","SmartShape_78","si11452"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":123},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11468"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_218","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_218","title":"Nationalities ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_219","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_219","title":"Nationalities ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_220","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_220","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20312","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20323","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20335","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_218","SmartShape_219","SmartShape_220","si20312","si20323"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":183},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20335"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_81","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_81","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11752","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"China ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11763","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_82","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_82","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11810","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Portugal ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11821","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_83","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_83","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Brazil ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11879","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_84","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_84","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11926","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Canada ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11937","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_85","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_85","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The  United States ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11995","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_86","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_86","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12043","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The  United Kingdom ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12054","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_87","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_87","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12101","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Mexico ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12112","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_88","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_88","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12160","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Chile ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12171","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_89","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_89","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12218","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Saudi Arabia ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12229","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_90","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_90","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12276","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Spain ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12287","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_91","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_91","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12335","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Peru ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12346","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_92","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_92","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12394","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Japan ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_93","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_93","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12453","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Korea ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12464","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_94","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_94","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12511","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Vietnam ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12522","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Canadian_95","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Canadian_95","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12549","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Canadian ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Chinese_96","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Chinese_96","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12576","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Chinese ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Brazilian_97","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Brazilian_97","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12603","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Brazilian ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Chilean_98","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Chilean_98","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12630","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Chilean ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Spanish_99","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Spanish_99","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12657","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Spanish ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"British_100","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"British_100","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12684","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"British ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"American_101","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"American_101","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12711","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"American ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Mexican_102","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Mexican_102","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12738","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Mexican ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Portuguese_103","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Portuguese_103","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12765","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Portuguese ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Vietnamese_104","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Vietnamese_104","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12792","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Vietnamese ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Korean_105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Korean_105","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12819","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Korean ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Peruvian_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Peruvian_106","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12846","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Peruvian ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Saudi_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Saudi_107","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12873","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Saudi ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Japanese_108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Japanese_108","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12900","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Japanese ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Gotonextslide_109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Gotonextslide_109","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12935","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12946","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Blocker_110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Blocker_110","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12974","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_111","title":"Click & Repeat the Nationalities ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13005","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_81","si11752","si11763","SmartShape_82","si11810","si11821","SmartShape_83","si11868","si11879","SmartShape_84","si11926","si11937","SmartShape_85","si11984","si11995","SmartShape_86","si12043","si12054","SmartShape_87","si12101","si12112","SmartShape_88","si12160","si12171","SmartShape_89","si12218","si12229","SmartShape_90","si12276","si12287","SmartShape_91","si12335","si12346","SmartShape_92","si12394","si12405","SmartShape_93","si12453","si12464","SmartShape_94","si12511","si12522","Canadian_95","si12549","Chinese_96","si12576","Brazilian_97","si12603","Chilean_98","si12630","Spanish_99","si12657","British_100","si12684","American_101","si12711","Mexican_102","si12738","Portuguese_103","si12765","Vietnamese_104","si12792","Korean_105","si12819","Peruvian_106","si12846","Saudi_107","si12873","Japanese_108","si12900","Gotonextslide_109","si12935","si12946","Blocker_110","si12974","SmartShape_111"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":123},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13005"}}},{"id":"si19620","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13221q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_25","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_26","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_112","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_112","title":"Where are you from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13221q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_113","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_113","title":"I’m from The United States. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13221q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13090","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_118","title":"Where is she from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13102","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_119","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13113","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_120","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13117","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_121","title":"She’s American ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13113_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"41","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s American\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13124","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_122","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13128","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_123","title":"She’s United Statesian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13124_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"43","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s United Statesian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13211","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_20","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13221q10","for":"Slide13221q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13166","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_95","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13221q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13179","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_96","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13221q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13221","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19620","Image_25","Image_26","SmartShape_112","SmartShape_113","si13090","si13102","si13117","si13128","si13211","si13166","si13179"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13221"},"question":{"interactionId":"13020","quizId":383,"title":"Where is she from?\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si19631","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13437q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_114","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_114","title":"Where are you from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13437q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_115","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_115","title":"I’m from Korea. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13437q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_27","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_28","roles":{}},{"id":"si13306","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_124","title":"Where is he from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13318","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_125","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13329","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_126","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13333","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_127","title":"He’s Koreanese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13329_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"180_44","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Koreanese\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13340","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_128","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13344","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_129","title":"He’s Korean ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13340_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"182_45","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Korean\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13427","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_21","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13437q11","for":"Slide13437q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_97","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13437q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13395","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_98","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13437q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13437","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19631","SmartShape_114","SmartShape_115","Image_27","Image_28","si13306","si13318","si13333","si13344","si13427","si13382","si13395"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13437"},"question":{"interactionId":"13236","quizId":383,"title":"Where is he from?\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si19642","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13653q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_116","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_116","title":"Where are you from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13653q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_117","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_117","title":"I’m from the United Kingdom. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13653q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_29","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_30","roles":{}},{"id":"si13522","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_130","title":"Where is she from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13534","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_131","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13545","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_132","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13549","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_133","title":"She’s British ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13545_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"180_46","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s British\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13556","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_134","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13560","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_135","title":"She’s Kingdominese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13556_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"182_47","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s Kingdominese\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13643","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_22","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13653q12","for":"Slide13653q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13598","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_99","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13653q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13611","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_100","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13653q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13653","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19642","SmartShape_116","SmartShape_117","Image_29","Image_30","si13522","si13534","si13549","si13560","si13643","si13598","si13611"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13653"},"question":{"interactionId":"13452","quizId":383,"title":"Where is she from?\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si19653","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13869q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_118","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_118","title":"Where are you from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13869q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_119","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_119","title":"I’m from China. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13869q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_31","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_32","roles":{}},{"id":"si13738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_136","title":"Where is he from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13750","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_137","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13761","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_138","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13765","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_139","title":"He’s Chininian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13761_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"180_48","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Chininian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13772","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_140","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13776","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_141","title":"He’s Chinese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13772_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"182_49","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Chinese\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13859","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_23","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13869q13","for":"Slide13869q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13814","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_101","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13869q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13827","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_102","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13869q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13869","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19653","SmartShape_118","SmartShape_119","Image_31","Image_32","si13738","si13750","si13765","si13776","si13859","si13814","si13827"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13869"},"question":{"interactionId":"13668","quizId":383,"title":"Where is he from?\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si19664","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14085q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_120","title":"Where are you from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14085q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_121","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_121","title":"I’m from Vietnam. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14085q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_33","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_34","roles":{}},{"id":"si13954","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_142","title":"Where is he from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13966","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_143","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13977","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_144","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13981","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_145","title":"He’s Vietnamese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13977_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"180_50","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Vietnamese\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13988","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_146","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13992","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_147","title":"He’s Vietnamian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13988_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"182_51","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Vietnamian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si14075","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_24","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide14085q14","for":"Slide14085q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14030","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_103","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14085q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14043","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_104","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14085q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide14085","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19664","SmartShape_120","SmartShape_121","Image_33","Image_34","si13954","si13966","si13981","si13992","si14075","si14030","si14043"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide14085"},"question":{"interactionId":"13884","quizId":383,"title":"Where is he from?\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si19675","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14301q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_122","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_122","title":"Where am I from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14301q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_123","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_123","title":"You’re from Canada. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14301q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_35","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_36","roles":{}},{"id":"si14170","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_148","title":"Where is he from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14182","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_149","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_150","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14197","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_151","title":"He’s Canadese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14193_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"180_52","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Canadese\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si14204","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_152","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14208","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_153","title":"He’s Canadian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14204_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"182_53","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Canadian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si14291","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_25","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide14301q15","for":"Slide14301q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14246","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_105","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14301q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14259","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_106","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14301q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide14301","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19675","SmartShape_122","SmartShape_123","Image_35","Image_36","si14170","si14182","si14197","si14208","si14291","si14246","si14259"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide14301"},"question":{"interactionId":"14100","quizId":383,"title":"Where is he from?\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si19686","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14517q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_124","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_124","title":"I’m from Brazil. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14517q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_37","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_125","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_125","title":"Where are you from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14517q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_53","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_53","roles":{}},{"id":"si14386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_154","title":"Where is she from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14398","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_155","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14409","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_156","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14413","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_157","title":"She’s Portuguese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14409_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"180_54","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s Portuguese\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si14420","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_158","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14424","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_159","title":"She’s Brazilian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14420_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"182_55","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s Brazilian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si14507","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_26","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide14517q16","for":"Slide14517q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14462","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_107","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14517q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14475","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_108","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14517q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide14517","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19686","SmartShape_124","Image_37","SmartShape_125","Image_53","si14386","si14398","si14413","si14424","si14507","si14462","si14475"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":156},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide14517"},"question":{"interactionId":"14316","quizId":383,"title":"Where is she from?\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si19697","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14733q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_126","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_126","title":"I’m from Portugal. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14733q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_127","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_127","title":"Where are you from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14733q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_39","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_40","roles":{}},{"id":"si14602","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_160","title":"Where is he from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14614","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_161","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14625","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_162","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14629","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_163","title":"He’s Portuguese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14625_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"180_56","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Portuguese\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si14636","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_164","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14640","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_165","title":"He’s Brazilian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14636_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"182_57","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Brazilian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si14723","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_27","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide14733q17","for":"Slide14733q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14678","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_109","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14733q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14691","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_110","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14733q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide14733","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19697","SmartShape_126","SmartShape_127","Image_39","Image_40","si14602","si14614","si14629","si14640","si14723","si14678","si14691"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":156},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide14733"},"question":{"interactionId":"14532","quizId":383,"title":"Where is he from?\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si19708","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14949q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_128","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_128","title":"I’m from Peru. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14949q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_129","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_129","title":"Where are you from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14949q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_41","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_42","roles":{}},{"id":"si14818","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_166","title":"Where is he from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14830","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_167","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14841","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_168","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14845","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_169","title":"He’s Peru ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14841_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"180_58","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Peru\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si14852","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_170","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14856","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_171","title":"He’s Peruvian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14852_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"182_59","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Peruvian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si14939","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_28","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide14949q18","for":"Slide14949q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14894","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_130","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14949q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14907","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_131","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide14949q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide14949","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19708","SmartShape_128","SmartShape_129","Image_41","Image_42","si14818","si14830","si14845","si14856","si14939","si14894","si14907"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":156},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide14949"},"question":{"interactionId":"14748","quizId":383,"title":"Where is he from?\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si19719","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15165q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_132","title":"I’m from Mexico. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15165q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_133","title":"Where are you from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15165q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_43","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_43","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_44","roles":{}},{"id":"si15034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_172","title":"Where is she from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15046","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_173","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15057","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_174","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15061","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_175","title":"She’s Mexican ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15057_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"180_60","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s Mexican\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si15068","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_176","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15072","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_177","title":"She’s Mexiconian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15068_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"182_61","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s Mexiconian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si15155","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_29","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide15165q19","for":"Slide15165q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_134","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15165q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15123","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_135","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15165q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide15165","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19719","SmartShape_132","SmartShape_133","Image_43","Image_44","si15034","si15046","si15061","si15072","si15155","si15110","si15123"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":156},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide15165"},"question":{"interactionId":"14964","quizId":383,"title":"Where is she from?\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si19730","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15381q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_136","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_136","title":"I’m from Spain. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15381q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_137","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_137","title":"Where are you from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15381q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_45","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_46","roles":{}},{"id":"si15250","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_178","title":"Where is he from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15262","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_179","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15273","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_180","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15277","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_181","title":"He’s Spanish ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15273_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"180_62","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Spanish\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si15284","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_182","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15288","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_183","title":"He’s Spainian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15284_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"182_63","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Spainian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si15371","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_30","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide15381q20","for":"Slide15381q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15326","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_138","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15381q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15339","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_139","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15381q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide15381","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19730","SmartShape_136","SmartShape_137","Image_45","Image_46","si15250","si15262","si15277","si15288","si15371","si15326","si15339"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":156},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide15381"},"question":{"interactionId":"15180","quizId":383,"title":"Where is he from?\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si19741","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15597q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_140","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_140","title":"I’m from Saudi Arabia. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15597q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_141","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_141","title":"Where are you from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15597q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_47","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_48","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_48","roles":{}},{"id":"si15466","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_184","title":"Where is she from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15478","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_185","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15489","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_186","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15493","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_187","title":"She’s Saudian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15489_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"180_64","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s Saudian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si15500","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_188","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_189","title":"She’s Saudi ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15500_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"182_65","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s Saudi\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si15587","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_31","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide15597q21","for":"Slide15597q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15542","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_142","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15597q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15555","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_143","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15597q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide15597","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19741","SmartShape_140","SmartShape_141","Image_47","Image_48","si15466","si15478","si15493","si15504","si15587","si15542","si15555"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":156},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide15597"},"question":{"interactionId":"15396","quizId":383,"title":"Where is she from?\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si19752","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15813q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_144","title":"I’m from Chile. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15813q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_145","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_145","title":"Where are you from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15813q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_49","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_49","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_50","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_50","roles":{}},{"id":"si15682","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_190","title":"Where is she from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15694","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_191","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15705","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_192","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15709","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_193","title":"She’s Chilean ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15705_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"180_66","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s Chilean\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si15716","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_194","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15720","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_195","title":"She’s Chilese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15716_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"182_67","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s Chilese\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si15803","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_32","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide15813q22","for":"Slide15813q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15758","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_146","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15813q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15771","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_147","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide15813q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide15813","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19752","SmartShape_144","SmartShape_145","Image_49","Image_50","si15682","si15694","si15709","si15720","si15803","si15758","si15771"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":156},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide15813"},"question":{"interactionId":"15612","quizId":383,"title":"Where is she from?\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si19763","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16029q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_148","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_148","title":"I’m from Japan. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16029q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_149","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_149","title":"Where are you from? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16029q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_51","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_51","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_52","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_52","roles":{}},{"id":"si15898","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_196","title":"Where is he from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15910","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_197","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15921","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_198","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15925","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_199","title":"He’s Japanian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15921_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"180_68","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Japanian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si15932","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_200","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15936","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_201","title":"He’s Japanese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15932_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"182_69","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Japanese\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16019","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_33","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16029q23","for":"Slide16029q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15974","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_150","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16029q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15987","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_151","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16029q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16029","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19763","SmartShape_148","SmartShape_149","Image_51","Image_52","si15898","si15910","si15925","si15936","si16019","si15974","si15987"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":156},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16029"},"question":{"interactionId":"15828","quizId":383,"title":"Where is he from?\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"SmartShape_221","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_221","title":"Drag & Drop ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_222","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_222","title":"Drag & Drop ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_223","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_223","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20429","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20440","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20452","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_221","SmartShape_222","SmartShape_223","si20429","si20440"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":183},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20452"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_153","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_153","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_154","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_154","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_155","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_155","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_156","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_156","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_157","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_157","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_158","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_158","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_159","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_159","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_160","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_160","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_161","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_161","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_162","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_162","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_163","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_164","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_164","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_165","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_165","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_166","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_166","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_1","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_2","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_3","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_4","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_5","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_6","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_7","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_8","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_9","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_10","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_11","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_12","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_13","roles":{}},{"id":"Line_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_14","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_167","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_167","title":"The United States ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_168","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_168","title":"Canada ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_169","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_169","title":"Spain ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_170","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_170","title":"China ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_171","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_171","title":"Japan ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_172","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_172","title":"Vietnam ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_173","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_173","title":"Saudi Arabia ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_174","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_174","title":"Portugal ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_175","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_175","title":"Brazil ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_176","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_176","title":"Mexico ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_177","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_177","title":"Chile ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_178","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_178","title":"Korea ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_179","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_179","title":"Peru ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_180","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_180","title":"The United Kingdom ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_181","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_181","title":"Drag & Drop the Countries to the correct location ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_1","title":"Type success text here ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_5","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide16700","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_153","SmartShape_154","SmartShape_155","SmartShape_156","SmartShape_157","SmartShape_158","SmartShape_159","SmartShape_160","SmartShape_161","SmartShape_162","SmartShape_163","SmartShape_164","SmartShape_165","SmartShape_166","SmartShape_167","SmartShape_168","SmartShape_169","SmartShape_170","SmartShape_171","SmartShape_172","SmartShape_173","SmartShape_174","SmartShape_175","SmartShape_176","SmartShape_177","SmartShape_178","SmartShape_179","SmartShape_180","SmartShape_181","Success_Shape_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":123},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16700"},"dragDrop":{"sources":[16397,16414,16431,16448,16465,16482,16499,16516,16533,16550,16567,16584,16601,16618],"targets":[16143,16158,16173,16188,16203,16218,16233,16248,16263,16278,16293,16308,16323,16338]}}},{"id":"SmartShape_224","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_224","title":"Matching ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_225","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_225","title":"Matching ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_226","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_226","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20546","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20569","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_224","SmartShape_225","SmartShape_226","si20546","si20557"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":183},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20569"}}},{"id":"si19862","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17134q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16855","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_202","title":"Match the Countries & Nationalities ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16867","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_203","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16874","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_10","title":"Countries ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_11","title":"A ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_12","title":"Portugal ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_13","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_14","title":"The United Kingdom ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_15","title":"C ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_16","title":"The United States ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_17","title":"D ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":"Peru ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","title":"E ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","title":"Spain ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"F ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","title":"Mexico ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_23","title":"G ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_24","title":"Brazil ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16964","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_25","title":"Nationalities ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16968","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_204","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16972","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_205","title":"Portuguese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16972ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Portuguese","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si16978","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_206","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16982","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_207","title":"British ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16982ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"British","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si16988","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_208","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16992","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_209","title":"American ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16992ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"American","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si16998","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_210","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17002","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_211","title":"Peruvian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17002ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Peruvian","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si17008","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_212","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17012","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_213","title":"Spanish ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17012ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Spanish","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si17018","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_214","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17022","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_215","title":"Mexican ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17022ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Mexican","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si17028","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_216","title":"G) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17032","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_217","title":"Brazilian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17032ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Brazilian","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si17120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_34","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17134q24","for":"Slide17134q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17075","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_183","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17134q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17088","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_184","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17134q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17134","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19862","si16855","si16867","si16972","si16982","si16992","si17002","si17012","si17022","si17032","si17120","si17075","si17088"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17134"},"question":{"interactionId":"16791","quizId":383,"title":"Match the Countries & Nationalities\r","text":"\r","type":"knowledgeCheck","ikc":true,"interactionType":"matching","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":[]}}},{"id":"si19873","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17491q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17212","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_218","title":"Match the Countries & Nationalities ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17224","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_219","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17231","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_26","title":"Countries ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_27","title":"A ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_28","title":"Canada ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_29","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_30","title":"Japan ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_31","title":"C ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_32","title":"China ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","title":"D ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":"Korea ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":"E ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_36","title":"Saudi Arabia ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":"F ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","title":"Vietnam ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_39","title":"G ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_40","title":"Chile ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17321","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_41","title":"Nationalities ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17325","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_220","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17329","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_221","title":"Canadian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17329ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Canadian","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si17335","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_222","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17339","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_223","title":"Japanese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17339ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Japanese","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si17345","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_224","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_225","title":"Chinese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17349ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Chinese","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si17355","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_226","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17359","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_227","title":"Korean ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17359ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Korean","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si17365","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_228","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_229","title":"Saudi ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17369ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Saudi","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si17375","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_230","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_231","title":"Vietnamese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17379ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Vietnamese","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si17385","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_232","title":"G) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17389","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_233","title":"Chilean ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17389ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Chilean","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si17477","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_35","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17491q25","for":"Slide17491q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17432","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_185","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17491q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17445","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_186","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17491q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17491","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19873","si17212","si17224","si17329","si17339","si17349","si17359","si17369","si17379","si17389","si17477","si17432","si17445"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17491"},"question":{"interactionId":"17148","quizId":383,"title":"Match the Countries & Nationalities\r","text":"\r","type":"knowledgeCheck","ikc":true,"interactionType":"matching","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":[]}}},{"id":"SmartShape_227","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_227","title":"Listening ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_228","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_228","title":"Listening ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_229","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_229","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20706","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20717","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20729","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_227","SmartShape_228","SmartShape_229","si20706","si20717"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":183},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20729"}}},{"id":"si19774","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17731q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_246","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_246","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17731q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23195","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17731q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23205","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17731q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17600","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_234","title":"Choose the correct Response ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17612","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_235","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17623","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_236","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_237","title":"Yes, I am. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17623_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes, I am.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17634","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_238","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17638","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_239","title":"I’m from Mexico. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17634_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"72","roles":{"answer":{"title":"I’m from Mexico.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17721","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_36","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17731q26","for":"Slide17731q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17676","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_188","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17731q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17689","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_189","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17731q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17731","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19774","SmartShape_246","si23195","si23205","si17600","si17612","si17627","si17638","si17721","si17676","si17689"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17731"},"question":{"interactionId":"17525","quizId":383,"title":"Choose the correct Response\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si19785","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17952q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_247","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_247","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17952q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23290","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17952q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23315","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17952q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17821","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_240","title":"Choose the correct Response ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17833","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_241","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17844","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_242","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17848","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_243","title":"It’s in Brazil. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17844_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"207_73","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It’s in Brazil.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17855","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_244","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17859","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_245","title":"No, it isn’t. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17855_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"209_74","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, it isn’t.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17942","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_37","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17952q27","for":"Slide17952q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17897","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_191","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17952q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17910","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_192","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17952q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17952","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19785","SmartShape_247","si23290","si23315","si17821","si17833","si17848","si17859","si17942","si17897","si17910"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17952"},"question":{"interactionId":"17746","quizId":383,"title":"Choose the correct Response\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si19796","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18173q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_248","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_248","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18173q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23384","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18173q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23409","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18173q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18042","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_246","title":"Choose the correct Response ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18054","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_247","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18065","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_248","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18069","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_249","title":"He’s from Peru. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18065_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"207_75","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s from Peru.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18076","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_250","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18080","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_251","title":"She’s from Peru. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18076_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"209_76","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s from Peru.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_38","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide18173q28","for":"Slide18173q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18118","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_194","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18173q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18131","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_195","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18173q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18173","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19796","SmartShape_248","si23384","si23409","si18042","si18054","si18069","si18080","si18163","si18118","si18131"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18173"},"question":{"interactionId":"17967","quizId":383,"title":"Choose the correct Response\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si19807","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18394q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_249","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_249","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18394q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23478","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18394q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23503","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18394q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18263","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_252","title":"Choose the correct Response ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18275","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_253","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18286","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_254","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18290","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_255","title":"Yes, I am. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18286_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"207_77","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes, I am.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18297","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_256","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_257","title":"No, he isn’t.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18297_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"209_78","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, he isn’t. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18384","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_39","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide18394q29","for":"Slide18394q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18339","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_197","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18394q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18352","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_198","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18394q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18394","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19807","SmartShape_249","si23478","si23503","si18263","si18275","si18290","si18301","si18384","si18339","si18352"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18394"},"question":{"interactionId":"18188","quizId":383,"title":"Choose the correct Response\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si19818","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18615q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_250","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_250","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18615q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23572","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18615q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23597","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18615q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18484","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_258","title":"Choose the correct Response ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18496","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_259","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18507","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_260","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18511","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_261","title":"Yes, it’s great. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18507_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"207_79","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes, it’s great.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18518","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_262","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18522","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_263","title":"Yes, it’s in the US. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18518_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"209_80","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes, it’s in the US.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18605","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_40","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide18615q30","for":"Slide18615q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18560","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_200","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18615q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18573","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_201","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18615q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18615","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19818","SmartShape_250","si23572","si23597","si18484","si18496","si18511","si18522","si18605","si18560","si18573"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18615"},"question":{"interactionId":"18409","quizId":383,"title":"Choose the correct Response\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si19829","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18836q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_251","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_251","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18836q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23666","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18836q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23691","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18836q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18705","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_264","title":"Choose the correct Response ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_265","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_266","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_267","title":"No, it’s in China. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18728_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"207_81","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, it’s in China.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18739","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_268","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_269","title":"No, I’m not. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18739_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"209_82","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, I’m not.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18826","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_41","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide18836q31","for":"Slide18836q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18781","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_203","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18836q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18794","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_204","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide18836q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18836","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19829","SmartShape_251","si23666","si23691","si18705","si18717","si18732","si18743","si18826","si18781","si18794"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18836"},"question":{"interactionId":"18630","quizId":383,"title":"Choose the correct Response\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si19840","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19057q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_252","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_252","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19057q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23760","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19057q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23785","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19057q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18926","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_270","title":"Choose the correct Response ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18938","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_271","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18949","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_272","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18953","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_273","title":"He’s from London. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18949_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"207_83","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s from London.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18960","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_274","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18964","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_275","title":"No he’s from London. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18960_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"209_84","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No he’s from London.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19047","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide19057q32","for":"Slide19057q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19002","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_206","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19057q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19015","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_207","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19057q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19057","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19840","SmartShape_252","si23760","si23785","si18926","si18938","si18953","si18964","si19047","si19002","si19015"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19057"},"question":{"interactionId":"18851","quizId":383,"title":"Choose the correct Response\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si19851","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19278q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_253","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_253","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19278q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23854","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19278q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23879","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19278q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19147","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_276","title":"Choose the correct Response ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19159","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_277","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19170","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_278","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19174","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_279","title":"It’s in Spain. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19170_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"207_85","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It’s in Spain.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19181","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_280","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_281","title":"Yes, he is. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19181_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"209_86","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes, he is.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si19268","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide19278q33","for":"Slide19278q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19223","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_209","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19278q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19236","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_210","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide19278q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19278","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si19851","SmartShape_253","si23854","si23879","si19147","si19159","si19174","si19185","si19268","si19223","si19236"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19278"},"question":{"interactionId":"19072","quizId":383,"title":"Choose the correct Response\r","text":"\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"SmartShape_236","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_236","title":"Take the Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_237","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_237","title":"Take the Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_238","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_238","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21081","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21092","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide21104","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_236","SmartShape_237","SmartShape_238","si21081","si21092"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":183},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21104"}}},{"id":"si22841","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21321q34"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_65","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_65","roles":{}},{"id":"si21147","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_282","title":"Question 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21159","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_283","title":"Are you from Canada? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21170","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_284","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21174","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_285","title":"No, I not. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21170_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"130_87","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, I not.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21181","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_286","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_287","title":"No, I’m not. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21181_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"132_88","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, I’m not.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si21192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_288","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21196","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_289","title":"No, am not. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21192_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"134_89","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, am not.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21203","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_290","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21207","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_291","title":"Yes, I’m not. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21203_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"136_90","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes, I’m not.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21277","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_44","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide21321q34","for":"Slide21321q34"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21283","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_44","roles":{}},{"id":"si21297","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_6","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide21321q34","for":"Slide21321q34"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21311","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_7","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide21321q34","for":"Slide21321q34"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21245","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_214","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21321q34"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide21321","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22841","Image_65","si21147","si21159","si21174","si21185","si21196","si21207","si21277","si21297","si21311","si21245"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21321"},"question":{"interactionId":"21127","quizId":383,"title":"Question 1\r","text":"Are you from Canada?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si22861","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21538q35"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_66","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_66","roles":{}},{"id":"si21364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_292","title":"Question 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21376","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_293","title":"What country is this? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_294","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21391","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_295","title":"The United States of America ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21387_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"122_91","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The United States of America\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si21398","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_296","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21402","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_297","title":"The States United ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21398_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"124_92","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The States United\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21409","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21413","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_299","title":"The America States ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21409_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"126_93","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The America States\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21420","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_300","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21424","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_301","title":"The United America ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21420_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"128_94","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The United America\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21494","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_45","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide21538q35","for":"Slide21538q35"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21500","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_45","roles":{}},{"id":"si21514","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_8","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide21538q35","for":"Slide21538q35"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21528","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide21538q35","for":"Slide21538q35"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21462","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_239","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21538q35"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide21538","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22861","Image_66","si21364","si21376","si21391","si21402","si21413","si21424","si21494","si21514","si21528","si21462"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21538"},"question":{"interactionId":"21344","quizId":383,"title":"Question 2\r","text":"What country is this?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si22881","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21755q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_67","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_67","roles":{}},{"id":"si21581","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_302","title":"Question 3 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21593","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_303","title":"Where ______ she from? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21604","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_304","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21608","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_305","title":"am ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21604_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"122_95","roles":{"answer":{"title":"am\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21615","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_306","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21619","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_307","title":"are ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21615_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"124_96","roles":{"answer":{"title":"are\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21626","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_308","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21630","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_309","title":"aren’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21626_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"126_97","roles":{"answer":{"title":"aren’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21637","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_310","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21641","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_311","title":"is ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21637_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"128_98","roles":{"answer":{"title":"is\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si21711","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_46","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide21755q36","for":"Slide21755q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_52","roles":{}},{"id":"si21731","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_10","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide21755q36","for":"Slide21755q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21745","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_47","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide21755q36","for":"Slide21755q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21679","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_240","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21755q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide21755","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22881","Image_67","si21581","si21593","si21608","si21619","si21630","si21641","si21711","si21731","si21745","si21679"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21755"},"question":{"interactionId":"21561","quizId":383,"title":"Question 3\r","text":"Where ______ she from?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si22901","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21972q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_68","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_68","roles":{}},{"id":"si21798","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_312","title":"Question 4 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21810","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_313","title":"_____ he from Brazil? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21821","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_314","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21825","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_315","title":"No, ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21821_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"122_99","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No,\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21832","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_316","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21836","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_317","title":"Are ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21832_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"124_100","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Are\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21843","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_318","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21847","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_319","title":"Is ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21843_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"126_101","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Is\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si21854","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_320","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21858","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_321","title":"Am ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21854_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"128_102","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Am\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21928","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_48","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide21972q37","for":"Slide21972q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21934","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_53","roles":{}},{"id":"si21948","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_49","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide21972q37","for":"Slide21972q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21962","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_50","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide21972q37","for":"Slide21972q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21896","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_241","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21972q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide21972","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22901","Image_68","si21798","si21810","si21825","si21836","si21847","si21858","si21928","si21948","si21962","si21896"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21972"},"question":{"interactionId":"21778","quizId":383,"title":"Question 4\r","text":"_____ he from Brazil?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si22921","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22189q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_69","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_69","roles":{}},{"id":"si22015","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_322","title":"Question 5 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22027","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_323","title":"He’s from Korea. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22038","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_324","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22042","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_325","title":"He’s Korean. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22038_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"122_103","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Korean.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si22049","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_326","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22053","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"He’s Koreanese. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22049_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"124_104","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Koreanese.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22060","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"He Korean. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22060_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"126_105","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He Korean.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22071","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_330","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22075","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"He’s Korea. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22071_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"128_106","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s Korea.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22145","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_51","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22189q38","for":"Slide22189q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22151","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_54","roles":{}},{"id":"si22165","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_52","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22189q38","for":"Slide22189q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22179","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_53","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22189q38","for":"Slide22189q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22113","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_242","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22189q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22189","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22921","Image_69","si22015","si22027","si22042","si22053","si22064","si22075","si22145","si22165","si22179","si22113"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22189"},"question":{"interactionId":"21995","quizId":383,"title":"Question 5\r","text":"He’s from Korea.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si22941","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22406q39"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_70","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_70","roles":{}},{"id":"si22232","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"Question 6 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22244","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"Where _____ Pele from? Is ______ from Argentina? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22255","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22259","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Is / she ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22255_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"122_107","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Is / she\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22266","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22270","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","title":"Is / he ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22266_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"124_108","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Is / he\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si22277","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22281","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_339","title":"Are / she ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22277_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"126_109","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Are / she\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22288","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_340","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22292","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_341","title":"Are / he ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22288_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"128_110","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Are / he\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22362","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_54","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22406q39","for":"Slide22406q39"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22368","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_55","roles":{}},{"id":"si22382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_55","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22406q39","for":"Slide22406q39"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22396","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_56","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22406q39","for":"Slide22406q39"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22330","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_243","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22406q39"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22406","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22941","Image_70","si22232","si22244","si22259","si22270","si22281","si22292","si22362","si22382","si22396","si22330"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22406"},"question":{"interactionId":"22212","quizId":383,"title":"Question 6\r","text":"Where _____ Pele from?\rIs ______ from Argentina?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si22961","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22623q40"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_71","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_71","roles":{}},{"id":"si22449","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_342","title":"Question 7 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22461","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_343","title":"You _____ from Paris?  I _____ from Paris too!  It ______ a beautiful city.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22472","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_344","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22476","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_345","title":"’re / ’re / ’s ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22472_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"122_111","roles":{"answer":{"title":"’re / ’re / ’s\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22483","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_346","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22487","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_347","title":"’m / ’re / ’s  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22483_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"124_112","roles":{"answer":{"title":"’m / ’re / ’s\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22494","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_348","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22498","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_349","title":"’re / ’m / ’m ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22494_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"126_113","roles":{"answer":{"title":"’re / ’m / ’m\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22505","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_350","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22509","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_351","title":"’re / ’m / ’s ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22505_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"128_114","roles":{"answer":{"title":"’re / ’m / ’s\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si22579","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_57","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22623q40","for":"Slide22623q40"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22585","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_56","roles":{}},{"id":"si22599","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_58","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22623q40","for":"Slide22623q40"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22613","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_59","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22623q40","for":"Slide22623q40"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22547","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_244","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22623q40"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22623","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22961","Image_71","si22449","si22461","si22476","si22487","si22498","si22509","si22579","si22599","si22613","si22547"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22623"},"question":{"interactionId":"22429","quizId":383,"title":"Question 7\r","text":"You _____ from Paris? \rI _____ from Paris too! \rIt ______ a beautiful city.\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si22981","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22840q41"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_72","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_72","roles":{}},{"id":"si22666","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_352","title":"Question 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22678","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_353","title":"Where’s this city? This is Toronto.  ______ in Canada.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22689","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_354","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22693","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_355","title":"He’s ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22689_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"122_115","roles":{"answer":{"title":"He’s\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22700","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_356","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22704","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_357","title":"She’s ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22700_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"124_116","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22711","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_358","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22715","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_359","title":"It’s ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22711_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"126_117","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It’s\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si22722","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_360","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22726","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_361","title":"They’re ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22722_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"128_118","roles":{"answer":{"title":"They’re\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_60","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22840q41","for":"Slide22840q41"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22802","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_57","roles":{}},{"id":"si22816","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_61","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22840q41","for":"Slide22840q41"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22830","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_62","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22840q41","for":"Slide22840q41"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22764","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_245","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22840q41"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22840","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22981","Image_72","si22666","si22678","si22693","si22704","si22715","si22726","si22796","si22816","si22830","si22764"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22840"},"question":{"interactionId":"22646","quizId":383,"title":"Question 8\r","text":"Where’s this city?\rThis is Toronto. \r______ in Canada. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si24533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24532q42"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_74","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_74","roles":{}},{"id":"si24358","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_364","title":"Question 9 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24370","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_365","title":"____ Dubai in Saudi Arabia? No, _______.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_366","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24385","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_367","title":"Is -- it is ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24381_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"122_119","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Is -- it is\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24392","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_368","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24396","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_369","title":"Isn’t -- it’s ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24392_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"124_120","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Isn’t -- it’s\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24406","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_370","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24410","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_371","title":"Is -- it isn’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24406_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"126_121","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Is -- it isn’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si24417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_372","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24421","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_373","title":"Isn’t -- it’s isn’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24417_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"128_122","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Isn’t -- it’s isn’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24477","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_63","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24532q42","for":"Slide24532q42"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24483","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_374","roles":{}},{"id":"si24497","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_64","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24532q42","for":"Slide24532q42"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24511","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_65","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24532q42","for":"Slide24532q42"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_254","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24532q42"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24532","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si24533","Image_74","si24358","si24370","si24385","si24396","si24410","si24421","si24477","si24497","si24511","si24459"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24532"},"question":{"interactionId":"24338","quizId":383,"title":"Question 9\r","text":"____ Dubai in Saudi Arabia?\rNo, _______. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si24755","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24754q43"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_75","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_75","roles":{}},{"id":"si24580","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_376","title":"Question 10 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24592","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_377","title":"Where’s ____ from? She’s from China. She’s ________.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24603","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_378","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24607","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_379","title":"he -- Chinese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24603_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"122_123","roles":{"answer":{"title":"he -- Chinese\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24614","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_380","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24618","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_381","title":"she -- Chinese ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24614_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"124_124","roles":{"answer":{"title":"she -- Chinese\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si24628","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_382","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24632","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_383","title":"he -- China ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24628_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"126_125","roles":{"answer":{"title":"he -- China\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24639","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_384","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24643","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_385","title":"She -- Chininian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24639_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"128_126","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She -- Chininian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24699","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_66","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24754q43","for":"Slide24754q43"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24705","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_386","roles":{}},{"id":"si24719","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_67","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24754q43","for":"Slide24754q43"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24733","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_68","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24754q43","for":"Slide24754q43"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24681","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_255","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24754q43"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24754","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si24755","Image_75","si24580","si24592","si24607","si24618","si24632","si24643","si24699","si24719","si24733","si24681"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24754"},"question":{"interactionId":"24566","quizId":383,"title":"Question 10\r","text":"Where’s ____ from?\rShe’s from China.\rShe’s ________. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si23050","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23072","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si23104","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si23061","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23068","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23100","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23116","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si23120","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23134","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23040","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23040"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_257","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_257","title":"End of Section Countries &  Nationalities ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_258","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_258","title":"End of Section Countries & Nationalities ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_259","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_259","title":"Back To Bridge ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24242","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back To Bridge ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24262","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back To Bridge ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24119","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_257","SmartShape_258","SmartShape_259","si24242","si24262"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":177},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24119"}}},{"id":"Pool427","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":427,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Countries&Nationalities","class":"project","title":"Countries&Nationalities","children":["Slide5126","Slide5434","Slide5845","Slide7706","Slide7895","Slide8080","Slide8265","Slide8450","Slide8631","Slide8812","Slide8993","Slide9174","Slide7250","Slide10297","Slide11468","Slide20335","Slide13005","Slide13221","Slide13437","Slide13653","Slide13869","Slide14085","Slide14301","Slide14517","Slide14733","Slide14949","Slide15165","Slide15381","Slide15597","Slide15813","Slide16029","Slide20452","Slide16700","Slide20569","Slide17134","Slide17491","Slide20729","Slide17731","Slide17952","Slide18173","Slide18394","Slide18615","Slide18836","Slide19057","Slide19278","Slide21104","Slide21321","Slide21538","Slide21755","Slide21972","Slide22189","Slide22406","Slide22623","Slide22840","Slide24532","Slide24754","Slide23040","Slide24119"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":383,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide5845q0","Slide7706q1","Slide7895q2","Slide8080q3","Slide8265q4","Slide8450q5","Slide8631q6","Slide8812q7","Slide8993q8","Slide9174q9","Slide13221q10","Slide13437q11","Slide13653q12","Slide13869q13","Slide14085q14","Slide14301q15","Slide14517q16","Slide14733q17","Slide14949q18","Slide15165q19","Slide15381q20","Slide15597q21","Slide15813q22","Slide16029q23","Slide17134q24","Slide17491q25","Slide17731q26","Slide17952q27","Slide18173q28","Slide18394q29","Slide18615q30","Slide18836q31","Slide19057q32","Slide19278q33","Slide21321q34","Slide21538q35","Slide21755q36","Slide21972q37","Slide22189q38","Slide22406q39","Slide22623q40","Slide22840q41","Slide24532q42","Slide24754q43"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":10,"passScore":8}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide5126","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide5434","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide5845","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide7706","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide7895","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide8080","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide8265","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide8450","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide8631","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide8812","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide8993","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide9174","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide7250","title":"Slide 13"},{"id":"Slide10297","title":"Slide 14"},{"id":"Slide11468","title":"Slide 15"},{"id":"Slide20335","title":"Slide 16"},{"id":"Slide13005","title":"Slide 17"},{"id":"Slide13221","title":"Slide 18"},{"id":"Slide13437","title":"Slide 19"},{"id":"Slide13653","title":"Slide 20"},{"id":"Slide13869","title":"Slide 21"},{"id":"Slide14085","title":"Slide 22"},{"id":"Slide14301","title":"Slide 23"},{"id":"Slide14517","title":"Slide 24"},{"id":"Slide14733","title":"Slide 25"},{"id":"Slide14949","title":"Slide 26"},{"id":"Slide15165","title":"Slide 27"},{"id":"Slide15381","title":"Slide 28"},{"id":"Slide15597","title":"Slide 29"},{"id":"Slide15813","title":"Slide 30"},{"id":"Slide16029","title":"Slide 31"},{"id":"Slide20452","title":"Slide 32"},{"id":"Slide16700","title":"Slide 33"},{"id":"Slide20569","title":"Slide 34"},{"id":"Slide17134","title":"Slide 35"},{"id":"Slide17491","title":"Slide 36"},{"id":"Slide20729","title":"Slide 37"},{"id":"Slide17731","title":"Slide 38"},{"id":"Slide17952","title":"Slide 39"},{"id":"Slide18173","title":"Slide 40"},{"id":"Slide18394","title":"Slide 41"},{"id":"Slide18615","title":"Slide 42"},{"id":"Slide18836","title":"Slide 43"},{"id":"Slide19057","title":"Slide 44"},{"id":"Slide19278","title":"Slide 45"},{"id":"Slide21104","title":"Slide 46"},{"id":"Slide21321","title":"Slide 47"},{"id":"Slide21538","title":"Slide 48"},{"id":"Slide21755","title":"Slide 49"},{"id":"Slide21972","title":"Slide 50"},{"id":"Slide22189","title":"Slide 51"},{"id":"Slide22406","title":"Slide 52"},{"id":"Slide22623","title":"Slide 53"},{"id":"Slide22840","title":"Slide 54"},{"id":"Slide24532","title":"Slide 55"},{"id":"Slide24754","title":"Slide 56"},{"id":"Slide23040","title":"Slide 57"},{"id":"Slide24119","title":"Slide 58"}]}